小姐
Miss?
我必须道歉
I have to apologize.
不必跟我道歉 但我肯定阿曼门诺派要生气了
Well, not to me, but I'm sure the Amish are pissed
北美洲戒律严谨的宗教团体
因为你让他们的装束显得像基佬
that you're gaying up their look.
我不够钱给小费
I don't have enough money for the tip.
真奇怪 餐厅的辣椒没干掉你
Weird. You survive the diner chili,
你却死在了服务员手里!
and it's the waitress that kills you!
但我能以另一种方式给小费 我是个灵媒
But I can tip another way. I'm a psychic.
所以 你已经知道
So, uh, you already know
你的尸体能在何处找到
where they're gonna find your body.
哦 拜托 我会死于一次大桥坍塌
Oh, please. I die in a bridge collapse
这事跟你没有关系
you have nothing to do with.
我能告诉你 你的未来
I can tell you your future.
哈! 你错了 我没有未来
Ha! You're wrong. I don't have one.
看见坐在那个位置的家伙没?
See the guy in the booth over there?
杰瑞德·莱托·随他去?
Jared "Leto Himself Go"?
杰瑞德·莱托 摇滚歌手 一头长发
他提出给我预示未来以作小费
He just offered to read my future as my tip!
哈! 你都没有未来
Ha! You don't have one.
小姐 让我看看你的掌心
Miss, let me read your palm.
先生 这时候过来可不是个好主意
Sir, coming over here right now is not a good idea.
我们不喜欢陌生人不给小费
We don't like to be stiffed by strangers.
六个月后也许可以 但现在还不行
In six months, maybe, but we're not there yet.
我是正规的灵媒
I'm a legit psychic.
我曾预言当时机到了
I predicted long hair was coming back
我的头发就会长到这个长度
in time to have long hair when it did.
好吧 你可以
Okay. You can read my palm.
我想要听到好消息
I could use some good news.
我本该抹护手霜的... 抱歉
I could also use some hand moisturizer... sorry.
我看到两个M?
I see two Ms?
你个贱人! 你一直私藏M&M's巧克力豆吗?
You bitch! Have you been holding out on M&M's?
哦! 是不是指男模特?
Ooh! Is it the male model
我在处理他的事
I'm managing
他还跟Max做爱
who's also making it with Max?
其实... 我看见一个小败笔
Actually... I see a small failure.
我收回我的话 你真的很棒!
I take it back. You are good!
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组  http://hdscg.com/ ==--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调: 。沫
翻译: morning 波特妹子 CC 酱油影
校对: 桃茜茜
这是你的巧克力柠檬酥皮水果甜点
Here's your chocolate lemon crumble.
虽然听起来它们不搭 但它们还是搭一起了
Sounds like it shouldn't work together, but it does.
这是Lady Gaga与Tony Bennett甜品
It's the Tony Bennett and Lady Gaga of desserts.
指乐坛搞怪天后Lady Gaga和国宝级歌手Tony Bennett的合作
Max 我能不能咬一小口?
Max, can I have just a wee bite?
吃一点点酥皮的碎渣?
A crumble of the crumble?
Caroline不让我吃任何东西
Caroline won't let me eat anything
因为我要拍写真大片
because of my big photo shoot.
快点!
Hurry!
不要咀嚼 不要品味 直接吞
No chewing, no enjoying. Just swallow.
吐出来!
Spit that out!
不!
No!
我说了 吐出来!
I said spit that out!
你现在是模特了! 真丢脸!
You're a model now! Shame on you!
贱人 他要饿死了
Bitch, he's starving.
他没吃吧 对吗?
He's not eating, is he?
我不希望一个棉花糖一样的男人
I don't want the Stay Puft Marshmallow man
出现在我女朋友的写真集里
showing up at my girlfriend's photo shoot.
我从周二开始就没吃过东西!
I haven't eaten anything since Tuesday!
今早 他试图吞下他的牙膏
This morning, he tried to swallow his toothpaste,
幸好被我阻止了
but I was right there to stop him.
干得好 亲爱的
Good, honey.
正因你冷血无情  才让我决定
That kind of heartlessness is why I've decided
让你担任"糕潮"新热门地段的
to make you the manager of our hot new location
经理
of the High.
天啊! 太令人激动了!
Oh, my God! This is so exciting!
终于有人看到了我的潜力
Someone's finally realizing my full potential,
而且那个人不是我!
and it's not me!
我能让Max做糕点主厨吗?
Will I be able to make Max head pastry chef?
还有 这个新地段在哪儿?
And where is this new location?
这一切都是秘密
Well, right now, everything's under wraps
而我六个月前是这种表情
the way my face was six months ago.
作为经理 你可以雇用你自己的员工
But as manager, you can hire your own staff,
我甚至可以让你挖走Max
and I'll even let you poach Max.
我还可以告诉你
I'll also tell you
新地点棒极了
the new spot is amazing.
很国际化 还是核心地段
It's international. It's a hub.
我说的是大型旗舰店
I'm talking major flagship.
亲爱的 我知道你很高兴
Honey, I get that you're happy,
但眼神交流已经够多了
but enough with the eye contact.
没有人能看着我的眼睛
No one can look me in the eye.
我是穿着香奈儿的美杜莎
I'm the Medusa in Chanel.
希腊神话中的女妖
我们做爱的时候 Max也不让我
Max doesn't let me look her in the eyes
看她的眼睛
during sex either.
我跟你说过 眼神交流是额外的
I told you, eye contact's extra.
Max 你听见没?
Max, did you hear that?
大型旗舰店!
Major flagship!
呃 刚刚是有人叫我"大旗"吗?
Uh, did someone just call me a major flag?
我猜是你 要是我没能
I think you did, and if I don't get to
跟你们俩去新地方
go to the new place with you two,
我要去跟人事专员说
I'm telling HR.
我说的是Hector Rodriguez 我的治疗师
That's Hector Rodriguez, my therapist.
你有兴趣加入新"糕潮"
Would you be interested in coming to the new High
成为我们的一员吗?
as part of our team?
你要是再说"我们的一员"
If you say "part of our team" again,
这整件事我就要重新考虑了
I'll rethink the whole thing.
我接受
I'll take it.
但我必须跟Max一起在前面
But I have to be upfront with Max.
我不喜欢在后面
I don't like it in the back.
顺便一提 我跟每个男伴都是这么说的
Which, by the way, is what I say to all my dates.
我也是!
Samesies!
这真是个好消息
Well, this is great news.
我们吃个饼庆祝下怎么样?
How about we celebrate with a piece of pie?
不行!
No!
Earl 我们有好消息 猜猜是什么
Earl, we have great news. Guess what it is.
不 不要 好 猜吧 不 不要 好 猜吧!
No, don't. Okay, guess. No, don't. Yes, guess, guess!
我们能不能快点?
Can we hurry this along?
我侄子今天上了莫瑞·波维奇的节目
My cousin is on Maury Povich today,
我想知道亲生父亲是不是他
and I wanna find out if he's the father.
因为这样 我就可以不付抚养费了
'Cause then I can stop paying child support.
抱歉 她有点紧张了
Sorry. She's a little amped.
自打她发现我们地下室的
She hasn't had good news to share
洗衣机会嗑药之后
since we found out the washing machine
她再也没有别的好消息能分享了
in our basement takes buttons.
Han 我们有好消息
Han, we have good news.
你们也会有好消息
Sure, you do.
那我就是在纽约尼克斯队打中锋的!
And I'm playing center for the New York Knicks!
你们最近有看尼克斯队吗?
Have you seen the Knicks lately?
他只是帮忙而已
He can only help.
根据我的考勤卡
Well, according to my time card,
我到这儿已经有六个小时了
I've been here for six hours already,
所以我要去后面 小睡一下
so I'm gonna head back and catch some Zs.
床是你的了 Max
The Mattress is all yours, Max.
嘿 各位 我们没想到会有人来
Hey, everybody. We weren't expecting company.
我过来
I came by
是和Oleg讨论婚礼细节的
to discuss wedding details with Oleg
就在我们嘿咻的时候
while we had intercourse.
这什么情况 兔子牧场吗?
What is this, the Bunny Ranch?
宝贝 这是你的吧
Baby, I think these are yours.
对
Yeah.
嗯 谢谢亲爱的
Yeah. Well, thank you, honey.
咱们能不能约法三章
Can we just make it a general rule
不要在餐厅里乱来?
that there's no fornication in the diner?
或是不在Han的家里
Or in Han's apartment, ever.
好了 Max和我有个非常好的消息
Okay, Max and I have some really exciting news.
是的是的 我们都知晓嗑药的事了
Yeah, yeah. We know all about the buttons.
Oleg啊!
Oleg!
你把座位安排都搞乱了!
I think you crushed my seating arrangement!
我倒希望是
I'd like to think so.
那么 回到我们
So, back to us.
不如回到工作怎么样?
How 'bout back to work?
Max和我...
Max and I...
该干活了!
Need to do some work!
就这样 说完了
There. End of news.
你这么急着去哪啊?
Where are you running off to so fast?
有人要甩卖小脑袋吗?
Is someone having a sale on smaller heads?
一会儿说我小 一会说我大 究竟哪样!
I'm too small, I'm too big... pick one!
我们要宣布好消息
Here's our big news.
你现在看着的是
You are looking at the manager
全新开张的糕潮点心店经理和甜点主厨
and the head pastry chef of the brand-new High location.
其实 他只能看到我们的膝盖
Actually, he's looking at our kneecaps.
好吧 看来是我说太小了
Okay, so we're going with too small.
如果你们俩不干了 我上哪找人替你们?
If you two quit the diner, how will I ever replace you?
除非我再雇佣... 随便谁都行!
Unless I hire... literally anyone else!
不 Han 我们晚上还是会在这里工作
No, Han, we still have to work here at night.
我们欠的债 比跟威尔史密斯老婆
We have more debt than Jada Pinkett-Smith
为她老公不在家找的借口还要多
has excuses for Will not being home.
但在新的糕潮店
But at the new High,
我们是发号施令的
we're gonna be the big bosses
头头儿们
calling all the shots.
是是是... 白天而已
Yes, yes... by day.
到了晚上 你们还是上酸菜的翠花
But by night, you'll be the coleslaw's bitch.
别听他的
Don't listen to him.
很明显 Han是嫉妒我们的成功
Clearly, Han just resents our success.
可不是! 女人何苦难为女人?
I know! Why can't women ever just be happy for each other?
哇哦 好热辣
Wow, that is really hot.
嗯
Yeah.
这个辣酱不那么辣
The milder salsa's right here.
我说... 哦!
Listen... oh!
女生们都开始吃东西了吗?
Do girls eat now?
哇哦! 莉娜·丹恩把一切都改变了!
Wow! Lena Dunham changed everything!
你们俩当中的哪个和那个模特上过床的?
Listen, which one of you is sleeping with the model?
我知道你们有个跟我说了
I know one of you said you were,
但你说的时候我没听
but I don't listen when you talk.
是她
She is.
这是个大规模的广告宣传活动
This is a massive ad campaign,
我不知道该怎么说
and I don't know how else to say this,
但我需要他的弟弟再大点
but I need his penis to look bigger.
哦! 好吧...
Oh! Yeah...
你用光照它是会紧张啦
It gets nervous when you shine a light on it.
有时我还听到她用吃的
Sometimes I hear her coaxing it out of its crawl space
骗它出洞
with treats.
想想办法
Well, do something.
自我读大学后就没碰过小鸡鸡
I haven't touched one since college,
就算碰也是为了找底下的钥匙
and even then it was just to look under it for my keys.
Max 带他到后场去 专业点
Max, take him off set. Be professional.
我还能怎么专业?
How professional can I be?
她是要我玩他蛋蛋
She's asking me to fluff his nutter.
嘿 Nash! 休息一下
Yo, Nash! Break time.
所以... Marie
So... Marie.
Joe跟你说了我的升职的新工作吗?
Did Joe tell you about my big new job promotion?
当然了 我们是拉拉
Of course she did. We're lesbians.
主要时间就是聊天
Talking is most of what we do.
所以我们统治了白天
It's why we rule daytime.
呃... 请原谅
Eh... pardon me.
你还能原谅 那外套罪不可赦
You, maybe. That coat... never.
我是找人的
I'm lookin' for someone.
你看起来像是"安吉拉的灰烬"跑龙套的
You also look like an extra from Angela's Ashes.
但这是私人拍摄地
But this is a private shoot,
也就是说我们在拍摄私人部位
as in we're shooting someone's privates.
我在找我儿子
I'm looking for me son.
好了 各位! 土拨鼠出洞啦!
Okay, people! The groundhog's outta the hole!
又多了六英寸啊
Six more inches of winter.
就是他! 那是我儿子!
That's him! That's me boy!
妈?
Ma?
哈?
Huh?
妈 你怎么知道我在纽约?
Ma, how did you know I was in New York?
不是吧 你在"今日秀"窗口看到我了
Aw, no, you saw me in the Today Show window,
对不?
didn't ya?
你脸书状态改成在"美国"了
You checked into "America" on Facebook,
你个熊孩子
you bleedin' idiot.
我直接飞到这个被上帝遗忘的脏乱差城市
I flew all the way and been lookin' for you day and night
日夜不停地找你一个星期了
in this dirty, God forsaken city for a week.
我要带你回家
I'm takin' you home.
女士 Nash可以自己做决定
Ma'am, Nash can make his own decisions.
他是成人了
He's a grown man.
没错 多亏我鼎力相助
Yep. Thanks to my handiwork.
他才不是什么成人 他刚十八岁
He's no grown man. He's just now 18.
下个月才高中毕业!
He's got his prom next month!
开玩笑么!
I can't believe it!
我睡了青少年!
I had sex with a teenager!
我都成了什么人 伍迪·艾伦?
Who am I, Woody Allen?
罗门·波兰斯基?
Roman Polanski?
基本上所有七十年代的电影导演?
Pretty much any of your big-time '70s movie directors?
你跟我无知的孩子上床了?
You had sex with me innocent child?
呃 没那么无知
Uh, not so innocent.
他让我脸红过几次
He made me blush a few times,
然后我发明了两种体位
and I have two positions named after me.
够了
Well, that's that.
你以后不许再见这个大胸放荡女了
You've seen the last of big booby dirty girl here.
我想反对 但你说得没错
I'd object, but when you're right, you're right.
可是妈 我喜欢纽约
But Ma, I like New York.
这里的人想拍摄我的小弟弟
People want to take pictures of me willy here.
这都是我的错
This is all me fault.
我从不该让你看"魔力迈克"的
I should have never let you watch that Magic Mike.
这下好了
That's great.
我现在没模特了
I don't have a model now.
完蛋了
I'm Seal.
等着我跟Joe说这事儿吧
Wait until I tell Joe about this.
你怎么能不知道他几岁?
How can you not know how old he is?
呃... 我能说什么呢? 我们是典型的恋人啊!
Uh... what can I say? We're a typical couple!
他在年龄上撒谎 而我假装他很有趣
He lied about his age, and I pretended he was interesting.
好吧 Max 等Joe来了
Okay, Max, when Joe gets here,
我就告诉她
I'm just gonna tell her
我照看一个未成年的臭小子
that me managing an underage twink
与我管理她这个卖超贵夹馅饼的餐厅
has nothing to do with me managing her restaurant
没有任何牵连
which sells overpriced twink... ies.
我相信她在这方面还是非常专业的
Yeah. I'm sure she'll be professional about it all.
专业?
Professional?
昨天有个女人因为穿了双廉价高跟鞋
Yesterday, she slapped a woman in here
在这里被她扇了一个耳光
for wearing cheap heels.
我知道 我的脸到现在还红肿着呢
I know. My face is still red.
她来了
Here she is.
早上好 Joe!
Good morning, Joe!
嗨 姑娘们
Hey, ladies.
显然 你们都被炒了
Well, obviously, you're both fired.
很显然
Obviously.
我能把帽子留着吗?
Can I keep the hat?
你不会想把它要回去的
You are not gonna want this back.
我头上出的汗就像野餐时的西瓜一样多水
My head sweats like a watermelon at a picnic.
求你了别为了Nash的事情炒了我们
Please don't fire us over the Nash situation.
这事儿我们也拿不准
It was out of our hands.
实际上 之前是被她手拿着了
Actually, it was in her hands,
而且只有18岁
and it was only 18.
你们两个让我的女朋友很难堪
You two embarrassed my girlfriend.
在蕾丝边的圈子里难堪
And embarrassment in the lesbian community
比没有养狗还要可怕
is worse than not owning a dog.
比和双性恋谈恋爱还要可怕
It's worse than dating Anne Heche.
哦 天呐 我们犯下了双性罪
Oh, my God. We committed a Heche crime.
我们要怎么弥补这件事?
How can we make it better?
只要那个孩子明天能到摄影棚来
Just get that kid back to the photo shoot tomorrow,
这一切就都能恢复正常了
and we're back in business.
还有Max 下次
And Max, next time,
远离他那还没有合法的部位
stay out of his barely legal business.
没问题 虽然不懂 但没问题
Done. Don't know how, but done.
不会让你失望的
You won't be sorry.
赶紧把他带回来 我告诉你们...
Just get him back, 'cause I gotta tell you...
Marie哭泣的脸?
Marie's crying face?
我可不想看到
Not for me.
好吧 卷心菜...
Well, coleslaw...
在我觉得我快没戏了的时候
just when I thought I was out,
你拉了我一把
you pulled me back in again.
Max 别对卷心菜说这些
Max, don't tell the coleslaw that.
别给它这个权利
Don't give it that power.
我让Nash回来的计划会成功的
My plan to get Nash back will work.
我们依旧有一个光明美好的未来
We still have a bright, bright future.
没错! 只有在早上
Yes! By day.
Han啊!
Han!
你还想在这个卷心菜桶里
Do you want to spend another night
呆一晚上吗?
in this coleslaw bucket?
不想 而且上次我如果没能
No. And had I not been able to
自己滚到大街上的话
roll myself out to the street,
我可能就窒息而死了!
I might have suffocated!
Max Nash和他妈随时都有可能到店里来
Nash and his mom will be here any minute, Max.
你真有必要把自己五分之三的胸都露出来吗
Do you really need to expose 60% of your boobs?
这不取决于我
It's not up to me.
这对白妞有自己的生活
These girls have a life of their own.
右边这位刚组建了一个翻唱Fleetwood Mac的乐队
The right one just started a Fleetwood Mac cover band.
你知道到我怎么发现的吗?
You know how I know?
因为我把胸罩脱掉的时候 它自顾自的走了
'Cause when I take my bra off, it goes its own way.
出自该乐队的歌名"go your own way"
g
你真的认为Nash的妈妈来这里
Do you really think you can get Nash's mother
拿Nash落下的行李之时
to change her mind when they come in
你能改变她的想法吗?
to pick up the rest of his stuff?
是的
Yes, I do.
因为我们两个有很多共同点
Because she and I have a lot in common.
我虽然不是爱尔兰人 但我也一样穷
I may not be Irish, but I'm dirt poor,
而且我也和一个嗜酒如命的人住在一起
and I'm living with someone who drinks way too much.
Max 你看
Max, look.
所有这些紫色的便贴
All those purple post-its
都是Spohie的家人和朋友
are Sophie's friends and family.
几乎没我亲戚的位置!
My family's nowhere to be seen!
就和我上次看美国人口普查一样!
It's like I'm looking at the last U.S. census!
姑娘们 快过来
Hey, girls. Come over here.
我们需要你们帮忙排这个座位表
We need your help with the seating chart.
筹办婚礼可比在满月之时
Yeah. You know, planning a wedding is more work
给Oleg的背上打蜡工作量要多
than waxing Oleg's back during a full moon.
Sophie 我现在有我自己的事情要解决
Sophie, I have my own issue right now.
好吧 那Max可以来帮我排座次
Okay. Then Max can help me with the chart
你就去担心你明显日渐变少的头发吧
while you go worry about your obviously thinning hair.
我全面透露一下
Uh, full disclosure...
上一次有人让我帮忙的时候
the last time someone asked me to help them with something,
我把他们的胡子吸掉了一半
I free-based half their beard off.
我收到Mash的短信
I just got a text from Nash.
他到了? 我去给他拿份儿童菜单
He's here? I'll go get him a kid's menu.
他们不来了
They're not coming.
他妈妈看到了我之前发给他的猥亵图片
His mom found the racy pictures I sent him.
"明天从JFK机场起飞
"Flying out of JFK tomorrow.
坐爱尔兰航空的早班机"
Taking the morning Aer Lingus"?
早上的"爱尔兰飞机"?
A little morning "Aer Lingus"?
不正是这飞机让Max陷入困境吗?
Isn't that what got Max in trouble in the first place?
好吧 我们要做的就是赶到机场
Okay, well, we just have to go to the airport
然后拦住他们
and stop them.
我会买好机票然后再把他们退掉
I'll buy us plane tickets and then return them,
就像我买鞋或者是汤姆·克鲁斯对待他老婆一样
like I do with shoes or Tom Cruise does with wives.
脱掉外套和鞋子!
Jackets and shoes off!
确认所有口袋里都没有遗漏物品
And make sure you check all your pockets.
不要让我因为一片口香糖戒严整个机场
Don't make me shut this airport down for a piece of gum.
这队比排队看"消失的爱人"都要长
This line is longer than the movie Gone Girl.
TSA是什么意思? "时间静止不动"
What does TSA stand for? "Time Stands A-still"
真有意思 从来没听到过这个版本
That's cute. Never heard that one before.
大多数人都会认为是 "这一坨翔"
Most people just go with "This Sucks Ass."
Max 别再大声喊叫了
Max, please don't yell out again.
人在机场会变得非常神经兮兮的
People get very jumpy in airports.
什么? 我喊的又不是 "我带了个炸弹"
Oh, what? It's not like I screamed, "I have a bomb"
女士 请你站到这边来好吗?
Miss, will you step over here, please?
我说笑的 我不是真的带了个炸弹
Oh, I was kidding. I don't have a bomb.
但是大家都觉得我... 有胸器
But I have been known to... be DA bomb.
Max啊!
Max!
求你了 如果我们走开了
Please, please, if we step away,
我们之前排的位置就没了
we'll lose our place in line.
我知道我们听起来像是来炸机场的
I know it sounds like we're here to blow up a plane,
但是实际上我们只是来阻止一个
but we're really just here to stop an underage kid
和她滚床单的未成年人离开这个国家
she had sex with from leaving the country.
我还是直接过来吧
So I should just come over there now.
没错 你刚刚被我亲手加入了
Yep. You just been hand-picked
"我不信任的人"行列
to join the "I don't trust you" dance party.
请出示你们的机票?
May I see your tickets?
天气不错 我喜欢你的发型
Nice day. I like your hair.
谢谢 我们只有脖子以上的部分
Thanks. We're allowed to be creative
可以自由发挥
from the neck up.
哦! 你们要去巴黎
Ooh! You traveling to Paris.
还是头等舱
First-class.
就穿这身?
In those jeans?
你买的是去巴黎的头等舱机票?
You got first-class tickets to Paris?
你疯了吗?
Are you insane?
我的手指自动选的
My fingers did it.
那是富家女的细胞记忆
It was rich girl cellular memory.
既然咱们哪儿都不去
And if we're not going anywhere,
那为啥不能假装去巴黎?
why can't we not go to Paris?
干嘛不假装要去卢浮宫?
And why can't we not go to the Louvre?
干嘛不假装要去住豪华酒店顶层套房
And why can't we not stay in the penthouse at the George Cinq
还能叫客房服务?
and not order room service?
现在说我不认识她是不是太晚了?
Is it too late for me to say I don't know her?
女士 你有没有携带爆炸物?
Ma'am, are you carrying any explosives?
我早餐吃的是墨西哥餐厅的剩菜
I had leftover Chipotle for breakfast.
那算吗?
Does that count?
对坐在你旁边的人就算
It does to whoever's sitting next to you.
法国航空113号航班
Air France flight 113
现在于24号登机口开始登机
will now begin boarding at gate 24.
Max! 那是我们的航班
Max! That's our flight.
法国航空113号航班
Air France, flight 113.
哦! 我打赌这飞机上
Ooh! I bet on the plane,
航空餐会有鱼子酱和贝利尼鸡尾酒
they'll have caviar and Bellinis.
你知道上面没有什么吗?
You know what won't be on the plane?
我们!
Us!
我们不去了!
We're not going!
你是不是偷抽了我藏在胸罩里的
Have you been smoking the half joint
那半支大麻?
I have hidden in my bra?
你竟然有大麻?
You have a joint?
我是说银行账户?
Bank account?
你带着大麻过了安检?
You went through security with pot?
我三年级就是带着大麻过的
I went through third grade with pot.
找到他了 Nash在那儿
There he is. There's Nash.
我想他妈妈肯定在问
I'm sure his mom is asking
能不能让他去参观驾驶舱 见见飞行员
if he can visit the cockpit and meet the pilot.
哇喔 他真嫩
Wow. He's young.
布鲁斯·詹纳变成女人
So young, Bruce Jenner has been a woman
布鲁斯·詹纳: 卡戴珊家族男主人 已宣布变性
也都有这些年数了
for most of his life.
Nash! 求你了
Nash! Please.
你不能走 我们今后的人生
You can't go. Our entire lives depend on
都取决于你能否完成那次摄影了
you finishing that photo shoot.
Nash Terrence O'Brien 你哪里都不准去
Nash Terrence O'Brien, you're not going anywhere.
否则我现在就抱你坐我腿上
Or I'll take you over my knee right here.
好吧 他很喜欢那样
Well, he likes that.
你...
Well, you...
你还真是逍遥放肆
You are just loose as a goose, aren't ya?
好吧... 你又说对了一次
Again... when you're right, you're right.
Max 让我和O'Brien女士谈
Max, let me talk to Mrs. O'Brien.
去登机口等着
Go up to the gate.
问问她们航班上会放什么电影
Ask what movie they're showing on their flight.
好吧 如果她们要放任何
Okay, but if they're showing anything,
我再强调一遍
and I mean anything
任何亚当·桑德勒的电影...
from Mr. Adam Sandler...
我就要上飞机了
I'm getting on the plane too.
拜托了 我求你
Please. I'm begging you.
你不了解我 我很高傲的
You don't know me. I'm a proud woman.
我唯一一次求别人
The only other time I ever begged
是为了从吹牛老爹的游艇下来
was to get off of P. Diddy's yacht.
连着开了三天的派对太久了
I mean, a party shouldn't be three days long.
小姐 你可以省省这些废话了
Miss, you can save your silly breath.
我要带他回家
I'm taking him home.
请Maeve O'Brien到登机服务台
Would passenger Maeve O'Brien please report to the gate desk?
Nash 也许他们同意把我们的座位
Oh, Nash, maybe they're bumping us up
从最后一排调到倒数第二排了!
from the last coach row to the second to the last coach row!
我就知道 我从未堕胎的行为
I knew I'd be rewarded for not having any abortions
肯定是会有回报的
in spite of me circumstances.
带上Nash... 在她分神的时候
Grab Nash... let's get out of here
我们快走
while I got her distracted.
Max 那是你干的? 怎么做到的?
Max, you did that? How?
我胸罩里的半支大麻没了
I no longer have the half a joint in my bra.
你用大麻贿赂了航空公司的人?
You bribed an airline employee with a joint?
我是指关节痛? 你应该多做伸展运动
Pain? Oh, you really gotta stretch out for that.
Max 这是绑架
Max, this is kidnapping.
他也没那么小 我在他这个年纪的时候
Oh, he's not that young. When I was his age,
已经抢了三家百视达影碟店了
I had already robbed three Blockbuster videos.
百视达影碟店是什么?
What's Blockbuster video?
天啊 我把一个孩子给毁了
Oh, my God, I screwed a baby.
好吧 我发条短信给Joe 告诉她
Okay. I'm gonna text Joe and tell her we have Nash
我们已经抓到Nash了 我还是打电话吧
in our custody. No, I'd better call.
在我们受审的时候 短信会出卖我们
That text won't play well at our trial.
对不起 没有告诉你我是如此年幼
I'm sorry I didn't tell ya I was so young.
但说实话 因为你也不成熟
But honestly, I didn't think it mattered
所以我觉得没关系
since you're so immature.
我知道你不成熟 但我成什么了
I know you are, but what am I?
好了 Joe对我们的绑架行动
Okay, so Joe was really impressed
非常满意 她把工作还给我们了
with the kidnapping, and she gave us our jobs back.
可是Nash 你被换掉了
But Nash, you've been replaced.
他们找了另外一个
They found another model
不会有家长干涉的模特...
who wouldn't give them any parent trouble...
一个大屌孤儿
a well-hung orphan.
大屌孤儿
A well-hung orphan.
主有所给 必有所取
Well, the Lord gives and the Lord takes.
那现在怎么办?
So what now?
你回爱尔兰 可以向你的朋友炫耀
Well, you go back to Ireland and brag to your friends
你与一个和艾克索·罗斯最好朋友的儿子
about having sex with someone who once had sex
艾克索·罗斯: 美国传奇硬摇滚乐队主唱
上过床的女人上过床了
with Axl Rose's best friend's son.
再见 Max
Good-bye, Max.
再见 Nash小可爱
Later, Nash Potater.
我觉得我会想他的
You know, I think I'm gonna miss him.
尤其是现在小朋友在六点前可以免费在奎兹诺斯快餐店用餐
Especially since kids eat free at Quiznos before 6:00.
我们走吧
Let's get out of here.
机场唯一的好处就是
The only good thing about airports
离开了它 就能去更好的地方
is leaving them for someplace better.
Max 我们下次再来 我会带你去巴黎
Max, next time we're here, I'm gonna take you to Paris.
先带我去厕所吧
Well, first take me to the bathroom.
早在电车遇坑颠那一下的时候 我就想上厕所了
I've had to pee since our tram hit that pothole.
至少我们能去个有格调的地方工作了
Well, at least we're gonna be working somewhere with class.
我很好奇那是在哪里
I wonder where it is.
Joe说那是个真正的中心 旗舰 国际化
Joe said it's a real hub, flagship, international.
没错 那就是八号国际航班候机楼!
Yeah. It's gonna be international terminal 8!
什么?
What?
这里?
Here?
我们要在这里工作?
We're working here?
我必须得弄清楚我前世到底
I've got to find out who I brutally murdered
残忍谋杀了谁 这辈子才要来还债的
in a previous life and make it up to him or her.
这太糟了! 这是唯一
This sucks! The one place
没人愿意送我们来上班的地方!
no one will ever give us a ride to work!
法国航空113号航班 最后一次登机通知
Final boarding for Air France, flight 113.
的确糟透了
Of course it is.
往好的方面看 这年头 很多飞机
Look at the bright side. These days, most planes
根本没法顺利飞到目的地
don't even make it to where they're supposed to go.
请头等舱乘客Caroline Channing和Max Black
Paging first-class passengers Caroline Channing
速来登机口
and Max Black.
那俩富家女真幸运!
Those rich bitches are so lucky!